

Ivini Ferraz

30/01/1977

PROJECT & PRODUCT MANAGER DIGITAL, COMMUNICATION AND MARKETING STRATEGIST

PROFILE

Senior professional with more than 15 years of experience in managing of transdisciplinary projects, and their digital strategies.

Marketing team leader with expertise in Web designer (UX), SEO, Google and Meta advertising, KPIs, Influencer Marketing, Copyright, Storytelling, WhatsApp MKT/Sales Inbound MKT, Growth Tools.

6 year of experience as

Costumer Journey specialist

CX/CDI/CRM/CX/CAM

- CDI Client Database Integration;
- Client Database optimization;
- CRMs setup and training;

<u>Digital Transformation</u>
<u>facilitator</u>: digitalization,
digital education, process
automation, data analyses and
visualization and agile
methodologies.

<u>Participation in Startups and</u> <u>Edtechs</u> using Lean and <u>Designer Thinking.</u>

EDUCATION

Graduated in "Project Management, Customer Journey and Agile Methodologies"

The Pontifical Catholic University of Parana (PUC-PR)

Master's degree in science: "Social 2013 Change and Political Participation"

São Paulo University (USP)
School of Arts, Sciences and Humanities (EACH)

Concentration area: - Social-spatial change, Public Health, Urban Sustainability, Climate Changes and Public Policies.

Undergratuated in "Art" School of 2001 Communications and Art

São Paulo University (USP)

Associated degree in "Publicity and 1994 Marketing"

Álvares Penteado Foundation (FECAP)

CERTIFICATIONS

Data Science Methodology and Tools International Business Machines -IBM

Analyst of Sustenability -ESG

Instituto Brasileiro de Sustentabilidade (INBS)

University Level Teaching Licensure

São Paulo University (USP).

Program of Improvement of Education (PAE) Training Modality

English Proficiency

União Cultural Brasil Estados Unidos United States Embassy

Licentiate in School of Education

Education School USL (FEA - USP)

2022

LANGUAGES



Portuguese (Native)



Spanish (Fluent)



English (Fluent)



French (Intermediate)

SOFT SKILLS

- Entrepreneur;
- Creativity:
- Self -Motivation:
- Teamwork
- Leadership Hand's on/ collaborative:
- Problem-solving;
- Strategic planning;
- Self-taught;
- · Committed with deadline;
- Innovator personality (ENTN)

FRAMEWORKS

- Agile Methodology;
- Lean Startup;
- Design Sprint;
- · Kanban Board;
- SCRUM:
- SWOT Digital Transformation Analyses.
- ESG diagnosis and assessment:

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present

Founder/ MKT Teacher **Product and Project Manager**

Players Multimedia School

playersdigitalschool.com

- Mentoring of Digital Transformation;
- Data Analyses and ERP and CRM integration;
- Courses: Mobile marketing, costumer services, e-commerce and social sales for almost 40 B2B fashion companies;
- Mostly, 4.000 students subscribed in LMS platform;
- Social project "FALA LOJISTA"; for women entrepreneurs (Digital inclusion).

2019-2021

Digital Strategist Consulting / Data Analyst

Buy2B - Behavioural Analytics · Big Data,

Software (Startup Credit consult B2B)

- Data Analysis, cleansing, enrichment (LGPD);
- B.I, ERP -CRM Integration;
- Inbound/Outbound strategy based in Data Analysis;
- I.T Team manager (Product Owner).

2021 - 2022

Head of Digital and Communication Transformation SINDHOSP (Union of Private Hospitals, Laboratories and Clinic's of the State of São Paulo)

sindhosp.org.br.

- SWOT analysis/Stakeholders interviews;
- Sprints Planning/Product Backlog/Agile Methodology;
- Team recruitment;
- Client Database Integration (CDI);
- Site's migration from ASP classic to WP. (17.000 pages);
- Increase 30% of page views (SEO strategy)
- Migration RD Station for open source Mautic (150.000 leads);
- Bitrix CRM and Contact Center setup; API WhatsApp Twilio;
- Reduction of I.T. and MKT costs (almost U\$70,000/per year);
- B.I API integration to improve a dashboard called "Health situation room", that displays public and private data, based on surveys with the Health sector.

2015 -2018

Co-Founder Digital Marketing Agency (Full stack)

2BDigital and Rumi Agency

Web Design · Digital Marketing · Ads- Video Production

TOOLS

Management: Jira, Trello, Microsoft Project, Bitrix24, Gantt.

Google:

Analytics 4.0, Search Console, Data Studio, Google Cloud., Google Earth, Google Trends

Open sources;

WordPress, PrestaShop, Mautic, Moodle, Elementor.

WhatsApp's Official API Meta Business Manager, Meta API for Developers, Google Ads, WhatsApp Business.

CRM (SAS)
Pipedrive, HubSpot, Bitrix24,
Salesforce.

Creation:

Adobe Premier and Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop and Canva.

Data: Power B.I, Google Data Studio, Jupiter Notebook, GitHub, and ArtGis, Excel.

Others: Zapier, Rd Station, ChatGPD.

CONTACT





iviniferraz@mail.com



+55(11) 98771-3268

São Paulo -SP-BRAZIL American VISA* 2019 - 2020

Head of Marketing and Digital Transformation

Grupo Planeta - (Events Franchising Group)

- Dashboard (B.I) displaying in real-time KPIs about 46 facilities;
- New website development and SEO Strategy;
- Client Database Integration (CDI) and optimization;
- Implementation of new Contact Center Omnichannel;
- Pipedrive CRM setup and training for sales representatives.

2016 - 2018

Designer Thinking - (CX) - Growth MTK

Post2B | Influencer Marketing Platform (Startup)

https://www.post2b.com/

- Designer sprint workshop facilitation (Mobile App prototype);
- OKR's cycle definition to measure Costumers Acquisition (CA);
- KPIs: Customer Acquisition Cost (CAC) and Life Time Value.

2013 - 2015

Project Manager

TECNOGEO - Integrated solutions
(I.T company focused on Urban Planning and Sustainability)

- Product delivered: Tourism Develop Plan. City: Salto (SP);
- Coordination of local team to regional data surveys.

2012-2013

Website Owner e Product Manager

Editora Gabel

Magazine's digitalization and regional shop guide (online).

2007-2014

ESG - Project Manager - (NGOs)

NGOs: Institute of Social and Environmental Entrepreneurs, "Ninhos" Institute and Ashoka Brazil.

- Proposal, fundraising and accountability;
- Educational coordinator for workshops and events (leader team);
- Local coordinator of "Youth Changemakers Program" and providing funding for 300 projects created by young entrepreneurs (Instituto Camargo Correia- Ashoka's sponsor;
- Consultant of Biosphere Reserve Council MAB (Unesco);
- CONSEMA (Environmental Council of São Paulo State), environmental entities's representant;
- Many projects for Children, Youth and Woman in vulnerability;
- Support for scholarships to undergraduate students by IDEAS;
- 3 granted awards to participants: "Young Journalist" by Santander, "Brazilian Youth Award" "Culture's Point" by Ministry of Culture (Brazil).
- Internation Intercultural Project in Europe: Uninawa (Valencia, Madrid).